[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 3, "question": "Do you have a name for this?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "a", "name", "for", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 4, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 5, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 6, "answer": "Revolution.", "answer_tokens": ["Revolution", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "What do you feel?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "Well, I think that there are -- we are passing through very interesting times.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "there", "are", "--", "we", "are", "passing", "through", "very", "interesting", "times", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Egypt", "Tunisia"]}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", ",", "DT", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "JJR", "JJ", ",", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "NNS", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "RBR", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "We're seeing revolution from the bottom up, is not being done through military means?", "question_tokens": ["We", "'re", "seeing", "revolution", "from", "the", "bottom", "up", ",", "is", "not", "being", "done", "through", "military", "means", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "I think what's happening in Egypt, Tunisia today, and perhaps elsewhere, these can be models for peaceful transition to more open, more accountable governance, and towards societies that offer more opportunities.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "what", "'s", "happening", "in", "Egypt", ",", "Tunisia", "today", ",", "and", "perhaps", "elsewhere", ",", "these", "can", "be", "models", "for", "peaceful", "transition", "to", "more", "open", ",", "more", "accountable", "governance", ",", "and", "towards", "societies", "that", "offer", "more", "opportunities", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "Oh, how long do you have?", "question_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "how", "long", "do", "you", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "I've got all evening, your majesty.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "got", "all", "evening", ",", "your", "majesty", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Egypt"]}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "So what annoys you most given your knowledge of that area?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "annoys", "you", "most", "given", "your", "knowledge", "of", "that", "area", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NNS", "PRP", "JJS", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "Well, I think there's a great deal of emphasis being placed by some who are perhaps don't have as nuanced an understanding and maybe lack a great deal of understanding on the religious component in what is taking place in Egypt today.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "there", "'s", "a", "great", "deal", "of", "emphasis", "being", "placed", "by", "some", "who", "are", "perhaps", "do", "n't", "have", "as", "nuanced", "an", "understanding", "and", "maybe", "lack", "a", "great", "deal", "of", "understanding", "on", "the", "religious", "component", "in", "what", "is", "taking", "place", "in", "Egypt", "today", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "Do you think -- do you think it's unhelpful when senior politicians here say such inflammatory things?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "--", "do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "unhelpful", "when", "senior", "politicians", "here", "say", "such", "inflammatory", "things", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "It's terribly -- it's unhelpful.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "terribly", "--", "it", "'s", "unhelpful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "Do you know the president?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "the", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "I have met him on a number of occasions.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "met", "him", "on", "a", "number", "of", "occasions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "What do you think of him?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "I think that he brought a new and fresh and open spirit to Washington, and I hope and pray that he's able to negotiate this very difficult town and all that it represents as a country.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "he", "brought", "a", "new", "and", "fresh", "and", "open", "spirit", "to", "Washington", ",", "and", "I", "hope", "and", "pray", "that", "he", "'s", "able", "to", "negotiate", "this", "very", "difficult", "town", "and", "all", "that", "it", "represents", "as", "a", "country", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "What would he have made of what's going on now, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "he", "have", "made", "of", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "now", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "I would like to think that had he lived longer that our region would not be in quite the state it is today.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "like", "to", "think", "that", "had", "he", "lived", "longer", "that", "our", "region", "would", "not", "be", "in", "quite", "the", "state", "it", "is", "today", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "CC", "JJS", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "What do you make of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "I think that they're having found each other and having obviously already worked so hard to build a loving relationship is one of the happiest and most wonderful developments, you know, in a long time.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "they", "'re", "having", "found", "each", "other", "and", "having", "obviously", "already", "worked", "so", "hard", "to", "build", "a", "loving", "relationship", "is", "one", "of", "the", "happiest", "and", "most", "wonderful", "developments", ",", "you", "know", ",", "in", "a", "long", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "You knew Diana quite well?", "question_tokens": ["You", "knew", "Diana", "quite", "well", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "UEEN NOOR: I knew her.", "answer_tokens": ["UEEN", "NOOR", ":", "I", "knew", "her", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Diana"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["'80s"]}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "TO", "CD", "NNS", ",", "IN", "JJ", ",", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", ",", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", ",", "NNP", "WRB", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "RB", ":", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "What did you make of her?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "I thought what she did in terms of bringing a focus to two issues, in particular, and this is not all, but AIDS and helping to break through the taboo that existed at that time in the '80s, '90s where people really didn't -- felt that they weren't safe in the presence of someone who might have contracted HIV, and the landmine issue that she made two key visits to landmine-infected countries.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "thought", "what", "she", "did", "in", "terms", "of", "bringing", "a", "focus", "to", "two", "issues", ",", "in", "particular", ",", "and", "this", "is", "not", "all", ",", "but", "AIDS", "and", "helping", "to", "break", "through", "the", "taboo", "that", "existed", "at", "that", "time", "in", "the", "'80s", ",", "'90s", "where", "people", "really", "did", "n't", "--", "felt", "that", "they", "were", "n't", "safe", "in", "the", "presence", "of", "someone", "who", "might", "have", "contracted", "HIV", ",", "and", "the", "landmine", "issue", "that", "she", "made", "two", "key", "visits", "to", "landmine-infected", "countries", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "What advice -- I mean, having been through this media frenzy, royal wedding, where you married a king, what advice would you give to young Kate Middleton, as she's about to marry the future king of England?", "question_tokens": ["What", "advice", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "having", "been", "through", "this", "media", "frenzy", ",", "royal", "wedding", ",", "where", "you", "married", "a", "king", ",", "what", "advice", "would", "you", "give", "to", "young", "Kate", "Middleton", ",", "as", "she", "'s", "about", "to", "marry", "the", "future", "king", "of", "England", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "I wouldn't presume to give her any advice.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "n't", "presume", "to", "give", "her", "any", "advice", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kate Middleton"], "LOCATION": ["England"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FAA"], "LOCATION": ["Kennedy"]}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "Have you enjoyed being a queen?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "enjoyed", "being", "a", "queen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "I -- as a young girl growing up during the Kennedy admission, my father was his FAA administrator.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "as", "a", "young", "girl", "growing", "up", "during", "the", "Kennedy", "admission", ",", "my", "father", "was", "his", "FAA", "administrator", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "So in a funny way becoming a queen enabled you to live your dream?", "question_tokens": ["So", "in", "a", "funny", "way", "becoming", "a", "queen", "enabled", "you", "to", "live", "your", "dream", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "It did.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "RB", "CC", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "Now that you're back, what can you tell us that perhaps you couldn't at the time?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "that", "you", "'re", "back", ",", "what", "can", "you", "tell", "us", "that", "perhaps", "you", "could", "n't", "at", "the", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "Well, I mean it was pretty intimidating to go out there and to see these thugs sent from, you know, central casting carrying these clubs with nails embedded in them, but I also frankly felt a little embarrassed about all the sympathy that we western journalists were getting.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", "it", "was", "pretty", "intimidating", "to", "go", "out", "there", "and", "to", "see", "these", "thugs", "sent", "from", ",", "you", "know", ",", "central", "casting", "carrying", "these", "clubs", "with", "nails", "embedded", "in", "them", ",", "but", "I", "also", "frankly", "felt", "a", "little", "embarrassed", "about", "all", "the", "sympathy", "that", "we", "western", "journalists", "were", "getting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "So the focus on the media are getting a few whacks for being overdone, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["So", "the", "focus", "on", "the", "media", "are", "getting", "a", "few", "whacks", "for", "being", "overdone", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "Fareed, let me ask you, in simple terms -- everyone has got all sorts of opinions here -- what is your gut feeling about what is actually happening now?", "question_tokens": ["Fareed", ",", "let", "me", "ask", "you", ",", "in", "simple", "terms", "--", "everyone", "has", "got", "all", "sorts", "of", "opinions", "here", "--", "what", "is", "your", "gut", "feeling", "about", "what", "is", "actually", "happening", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ":", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "RB", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "I think what's happening now -- it's fascinating.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "what", "'s", "happening", "now", "--", "it", "'s", "fascinating", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "How do you think history will judge him?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "think", "history", "will", "judge", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "I think he'll probably be seen as a care taker.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "'ll", "probably", "be", "seen", "as", "a", "care", "taker", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "What do you make of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "Well, I mean, I think that people here misunderstand the Muslim Brotherhood to some extent.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "I", "think", "that", "people", "here", "misunderstand", "the", "Muslim", "Brotherhood", "to", "some", "extent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "I think, at the end of the day, the administration is handling it roughly right.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", ",", "at", "the", "end", "of", "the", "day", ",", "the", "administration", "is", "handling", "it", "roughly", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Cairo"]}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "Why is that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "The Arab street, especially in Cairo, I think you're finding that, no, they are not going to negotiate until Mubarak steps down.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "Arab", "street", ",", "especially", "in", "Cairo", ",", "I", "think", "you", "'re", "finding", "that", ",", "no", ",", "they", "are", "not", "going", "to", "negotiate", "until", "Mubarak", "steps", "down", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "ORGAN: But giving that Omar Suleiman, who is the vice president that you I think believe would be best placed to take over -- given he's been pretty much at the right hand of Mubarak for years now -- some would argue that using a wacky races terminology, he's just motley to dastardly, isn't he?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "But", "giving", "that", "Omar", "Suleiman", ",", "who", "is", "the", "vice", "president", "that", "you", "I", "think", "believe", "would", "be", "best", "placed", "to", "take", "over", "--", "given", "he", "'s", "been", "pretty", "much", "at", "the", "right", "hand", "of", "Mubarak", "for", "years", "now", "--", "some", "would", "argue", "that", "using", "a", "wacky", "races", "terminology", ",", "he", "'s", "just", "motley", "to", "dastardly", ",", "is", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "MD", "VB", "JJS", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RP", ":", "VBN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", "RB", ":", "DT", "MD", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "No, but he's respected in the Arab world.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "but", "he", "'s", "respected", "in", "the", "Arab", "world", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Omar Suleiman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "Also in relation to Israel, what is your view of how we protect Israel, given this political void we have in Egypt?", "question_tokens": ["Also", "in", "relation", "to", "Israel", ",", "what", "is", "your", "view", "of", "how", "we", "protect", "Israel", ",", "given", "this", "political", "void", "we", "have", "in", "Egypt", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", ",", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "Well, that's two separate questions.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "two", "separate", "questions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel", "Israel", "Egypt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "Why was that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "was", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "Well, they knew that problems were brewing.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "knew", "that", "problems", "were", "brewing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["North Africa"]}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 400, "question": "Are we now seeing a newer, better way of revolution, driven from the bottom up through the people, than perhaps, you know, a revolution driven by the Americans taking military into these countries?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "we", "now", "seeing", "a", "newer", ",", "better", "way", "of", "revolution", ",", "driven", "from", "the", "bottom", "up", "through", "the", "people", ",", "than", "perhaps", ",", "you", "know", ",", "a", "revolution", "driven", "by", "the", "Americans", "taking", "military", "into", "these", "countries", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJR", ",", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 401, "answer": "From North Africa all the across the world of Islam, it's a new day.", "answer_tokens": ["From", "North", "Africa", "all", "the", "across", "the", "world", "of", "Islam", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "new", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "What was your reaction as a fellow astronaut to that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "reaction", "as", "a", "fellow", "astronaut", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "Well, I'm very proud that he made the decision that he did.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "very", "proud", "that", "he", "made", "the", "decision", "that", "he", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "How are you going to keep Arianna sexy?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "going", "to", "keep", "Arianna", "sexy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "Arianna is very sexy.", "answer_tokens": ["Arianna", "is", "very", "sexy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Arianna"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 472, "question": "And it will stay that way?", "question_tokens": ["And", "it", "will", "stay", "that", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "I think --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "It didn't exactly work with \"The Times of London,\" did it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "did", "n't", "exactly", "work", "with", "``", "The", "Times", "of", "London", ",", "''", "did", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "''", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "Well, interesting point.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "interesting", "point", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["London"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ",", "IN", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "Are you too?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "too", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "One of the future things we're looking at, though, now is I think the model has really been fueled by free content and will be for some period of time.", "answer_tokens": ["One", "of", "the", "future", "things", "we", "'re", "looking", "at", ",", "though", ",", "now", "is", "I", "think", "the", "model", "has", "really", "been", "fueled", "by", "free", "content", "and", "will", "be", "for", "some", "period", "of", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 492, "question": "how Much does it make at the moment, profit?", "question_tokens": ["how", "Much", "does", "it", "make", "at", "the", "moment", ",", "profit", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "\"The Huffington Post?\"", "answer_tokens": ["``", "The", "Huffington", "Post", "?", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBD", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "Is any of that actual profit?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "any", "of", "that", "actual", "profit", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "Yes, and there was profit there.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "and", "there", "was", "profit", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["AOL"]}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "NN", "RB", "RB", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "POS", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "It looks like you've won and you've lost, haven't you?", "question_tokens": ["It", "looks", "like", "you", "'ve", "won", "and", "you", "'ve", "lost", ",", "have", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "Piers, let me tell you something right now -- and I've said this to our investors -- if you believe in the future of content and you believe in the future of the Internet, AOL's the best buy.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "let", "me", "tell", "you", "something", "right", "now", "--", "and", "I", "'ve", "said", "this", "to", "our", "investors", "--", "if", "you", "believe", "in", "the", "future", "of", "content", "and", "you", "believe", "in", "the", "future", "of", "the", "Internet", ",", "AOL", "'s", "the", "best", "buy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "Honestly?", "question_tokens": ["Honestly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "There's so many things to think.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "so", "many", "things", "to", "think", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "ORGAN: When you see their, do you think monster, vile, greedy, horrible?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "When", "you", "see", "their", ",", "do", "you", "think", "monster", ",", "vile", ",", "greedy", ",", "horrible", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", ",", "JJ", ",", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "We certainly see a person who is where he is today absolutely because we approached him with our idea, our business plan and two years worth of work.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "certainly", "see", "a", "person", "who", "is", "where", "he", "is", "today", "absolutely", "because", "we", "approached", "him", "with", "our", "idea", ",", "our", "business", "plan", "and", "two", "years", "worth", "of", "work", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "Anderson, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Anderson", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "I'm doing all right, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "doing", "all", "right", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "PRP", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "Did you call them Winklevii, by the way?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "call", "them", "Winklevii", ",", "by", "the", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "Well, I did call them that, but they take exception to that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "did", "call", "them", "that", ",", "but", "they", "take", "exception", "to", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Winklevii"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "So, Anderson, can I just ask, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "Anderson", ",", "can", "I", "just", "ask", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "I'm OK.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anderson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "What did you mean by that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "mean", "by", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "Well, I think I feel guilty leaving, frankly.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "I", "feel", "guilty", "leaving", ",", "frankly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]